const jokes = [
    {
        question: "What has more letters than the alphabet?",
        answer: "post office",
        comment: "The post office, of course!"
    },
    {
        question: "What do you call an American bee?",
        answer: "usb|usbee|usbee|us-bee",
        comment: "A US bee... USB..."
    },
    {
        question: "What do you call a witch who lives at the beach?",
        answer: "sandwich|sandwitch|sand-witch|sand-witch",
        comment: "A Sand-witch! ü•™"
    },
    {
        question: "Why couldn't the bicycle stand up by itself?",
        answer: "two-tired|too tired|two tired|two tyred|too tyred|two-tyred|too-tyred",
        comment: "It was two-tired!"
    },
    {
        question: "What do you call a man without a body but has a nose?",
        answer: "no-body nose|nobody nose|no body nose|no-body knows|nobody knows|no body knows|",
        comment: "No-body nose... Nobody knows"
    },
    {
        question: "Which bear is the most condescending?",
        answer: "pan-duh|panda",
        comment: "Pan-duh! üêº"
    },
    {
        question: "What‚Äôs brown and sticky?",
        answer: "stick",
        comment: "A... stick LOL"
    },
    {
        question: "What do you call a pudgy psychic?",
        answer: "four-chin teller|fortune teller",
        comment: "A four-chin teller..."
    },
    {
        question: "Why are elevator jokes so classic and good?",
        answer: "levels",
        comment: "Because they work on so many levels. All the right buttons are pushed."
    },
    {
        question: "Why is Peter Pan always flying?",
        answer: "neverlands|never lands|neverland|never land",
        comment: "He neverlands!"
    },
    {
        question: "What kind of shoes does a lazy person wear?",
        answer: "loafers|loafer",
        comment: "Loafers, of course!"
    },
    {
        question: "What‚Äôs red and smells like blue paint?",
        answer: "red paint",
        comment: "Red paint, obviously!"
    },
]